

Alexandro Almeida da Silva

Hope Access Supervisor Level 3

- + 55 21 99652-1664
- alexandro.inspetor@gmail.com
- Rio de Janeiro/Brazil
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/alexandro-almeida-61559727/

PROFILE

Level 3 IRATA Maintenance and Assembly Supervisor, with more than 17 years of experience in the industrial area, on oil platforms. Specialist in inspections, boilermaking, anchoring systems, development of rope access means. Working on the implementation of procedures, pricing rate and reports for control of rope access equipment, rope access system, Height Rescue and First Aid.

Mechanical technician with several courses that permeate the area, making me a versatile professional, with readiness with new technologies.

Adaptable, with strong teamwork, team management, proactivity and leadership skills. Available to travel and for flexible work schedule.

EDUCATION

Associate Degrees - Mechanics Rezende Rammel Community College Ago 2015

TRAINING

- Hope Access IRATA Level 3
- Welding Inspector FBTS – Rio de Janeiro
- Magnetic Particle Inspection Inspector Level 2 SNQC – 7119
- Liquid Penetrant Inspection Inspector Level 2 SNQC – 7119
- Inspection by Thickness Measurement Inspector Level 1 SQNC 7119

WORK HISTORY

IRATA Level 3 Supervisor OCYAN S.A.

Apr 2022 - Dec 2023

• Electronic assembly and installation supervisor

Hope Access Supervisor C.S.E. MECANICA E INSTRUMENTAÇÃO LTDA

Jul 2021 – Mar 2022

· Construction, assembly and repair supervisor

Boilmaker Hope Access Supervisor ELFE OPEREÇÃO E MANUTENÇÃO S.A

Nov 2020 – Jun 2021

· Construction, assembly and repair supervisor

Hope Access Supervisor WOOD GROUP ENG. BRASIL LTDA

Mar 2020 – Jun 2020

· Construction, assembly and repair supervisor

1

A/S Alexandro Almeida da Silva

Hope Access Supervisor Level 3

TRAINING

- CBSP Salvatagem SEPAFMAR
- T-HUET

RelyOn Nutec

- Hot Work Observer (Fire Watch)
 Somatick
- NR-37 Segurança e Saúde em Plat. de Petróleo EVO

SKILLS

- Teamwork
- Communication
- Proactivity
- Leadership
- Material Acquisition
- Safety Management

DOCUMENTS

• Valid Passport

WORK HISTORY

IRATA 3 Supervisor

OES SERVIÇOS E EQUIP. DE PETROLEO E GAS LTDA

Dec 2019 - Mar 2020

- · Construction, assembly and repair supervisor
- Inspection with NDT techniques on equipment and tools
- Handling and lifting of loads (Rigging)

IRATA 3 Supervisor

INTEGRAR - CONSTRUÇAO E MONTAGEM

Nov 2017 - Sep 2019

- · Supervision of climbers and Boilmakers and paint team
- · Construction on floating hotels UMCF / UMCP / UMMA/ UMLI

IRATA 3 Supervisor

UTC ENGENHARIA S/A

Apr 2014 - Aug 2017

- · Construction, assembly and repair supervisor
- · Boilmaker and industrial painting work, by hope access
- · Construction on floating hotels UMCF / UMSJ / UMAR

IRATA 3 Supervisor – LP/PM/ME Inspector IRM SERVIÇOS LTDA

Apr 2011 - Apr 2014

- · Boilmaker and industrial painting work, by hope access, on-shore e off-shore
- Drill tools inspections, by hope access
- Team supervision and reports
- Derrick Inspection and Drop Objects

LP / PM / ME / IRATA Inspector – IRATA level 2 SISTAC SISTEMAS DE ACESSO S.A

Jun 2010 – Apr 2011

- Inspection with NDT techniques on equipment and tools
- Inspections on rigid and flexible risers

LP/ PM Inspector - IRATA level I GAIA OPERAÇÕES LTDA

Nov 2006 - May 2010

 Inspection with NDT techniques on boilmake, equipment and tools, on Oil and Gas Platforms (PPM-1 and P-09)